http://www.coloradobaskets.com/privacy-policy

Be sure to include your desired delivery date in the Special Instructions box!Colorado in a BasketColorado in a BasketColorado in a BasketColorado in a BasketSign InCreate AccountOrdersMy AccountSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comOrdersMy AccountSign outColorado in a BasketColorado in a BasketColorado in a BasketColorado in a BasketHomeAboutStoreCorporateShippingGalleryContactMoreHomeAboutStoreCorporateShippingGalleryContactSign InCreate AccountOrdersMy AccountSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comOrdersMy AccountSign outSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comHomeAboutStoreCorporateShippingGalleryContactAccountOrdersMy AccountSign outSign InOrdersMy Account
Privacy PolicyThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Coloradobaskets.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:· See what data we have about you, if any.· Change/correct any data we have about you.· Have us delete any data we have about you.· Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 303-664-1401 or Coloradobasket@hotmail.com.Orders We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Powered by Wilbur the CatDesigned and Managed by Ryrad LLC © 2020 Colorado in a Basket - All Rights ReservedHomeAboutStoreCorporateShippingGalleryContactPrivacy PolicyLegal
